Good morning.
Hey, don't sound so draggy.
Always arrive fifteen minutes early.
It's called being a grown-up.
Well...
Last night's drinking party ran a bit late.
Please forgive me!
Well, It's true that such social
events are part of the job,
but you need to have limits.
Huh?
Isn't Kamegawa-kun here yet?
You're right.
He's usually early.
Senpai's been telling me for the past six
months to arrive fifteen minutes early, so...
This is unusual for him.
I mean, technically, he ain't late,
so it ain't a problem, but...
ABOUT MY SHIFT TODAY
HOPE YOU ARE WELL. I APOLOGIZE, BUT—
YU KAMEGAWA > AZUSA KANNAWA:
ABOUT MY SHIFT TODAY
I'm so sorry.
I haven't been feeling well since last night,
so I'm going to see a doctor before work.
I'll be back in time for our afternoon meeting.
Warm regards.
Go rest, you idiot!
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
EPISODE 10: I'M GONNA VISIT MY JUNIOR!
"I'm Gonna Visit My Junior!"
Kannawa-senpai!
Hmm?
Oh.
Why are you two together?
Well, because...
we became besties after
our trip to the spa!
Yeah!
Is that so?
We were chatting away while
eating our post-bath ice cream.
That cold ice cream after a hot bath...
Truly a blissful moment!
Eating with you made it
even more delicious!
It was so fun. We should go again.
People with high communication
skills become friends so fast!
By the way, are you by yourself today?
Huh?
You're usually with Kamegawa-kun.
He's taking the day off because he's unwell.
He tried to come in, and I had to stop him.
I see.
It's been getting colder lately, after all.
Maintaining one's health is part of the job.
What if he made his condition worse?
Wh-What?
You two are acting weird!
This is a good opportunity.
Why don't you go visit your
precious junior tomorrow?
What?!
It would be a nuisance for me to
bother him out of the blue like that.
I'm just his senior.
That's not true!
I'm sure he'll be happy to have the senpai
he respects so much visiting him!
RESPECT...?!
Respect?
But I don't know his address.
I know where he lives! I swung by his place
on our way back from the newbies' meeting.
But his girlfriend could be visiting.
Nope!
There's no way!
But...
Aren't you worried about him?
You're such a cold-hearted mentor.
Of course I'm worried!
Then let's go!
It's decided.
In the end... I showed up.
Maybe I am being a nuisance.
No.
Since I came all the way here...
CALL
Drop it off and go home.
Um, excuse me?
Kamegawa's... girlfriend?
Are you visiting
my big brother, perhaps?
What? B-Brother?
Oh! Are you his girlfriend?
No!
I'm not!
I'm not his girlfriend!
Yes?
S-Senpai?!
She said she came to visit you!
What?
It's pretty cramped, but come on in.
W-Wait just a minute!
Sorry.
I only wanted to drop these
things off and head home.
N-No!
It's messy, but if you don't
mind... please come in!
I'm Yuki, his little sister!
KAMEGAWA'S LITTLE SISTER
YUKI KAMEGAWA
I-I'm Azusa Kannawa.
I've been your brother's mentor
since this spring.
I started university this spring,
so I visit here from time to time!
Senpai!
You don't need to introduce
yourself so politely to her!
R-Really?
Lucky you. You have such a pretty mentor.
Cut it out.
Please take a seat over there.
It's a bit cramped, though.
Th-Thank you.
Is barley tea okay with you, Senpai?
Don't worry about me.
You're sick, so you should be resting.
Don't worry!
I feel a lot better after
sleeping all day yesterday.
But...
The doctor also said it was
nothing to worry about.
I see. That's great.
EGG RICE PORRIDGE
Enough with all this sick talk!
She came all this way. Time to serve our guest.
Wow!
She got you all kinds of things!
Is it okay if I take them out now?
Of course.
Okay!
Time for your cute little sister
to prepare something delicious
for her poor, sickly brother.
Huh?!
No, you can—
I...
I'll help, too!
What?!
Let's begin.
What should we prep first?
Hmm...
Let's wash the apples first.
Okay! Then I'll get the dish soap and—
Don't use that!
Oh, really? Then...
Huh?!
I didn't know Kamegawa had a little sister.
Sorry about before!
I just assumed you were his girlfriend—
Hey!
Say any more than that, and I'll get angry.
Ooh, scary!
All right! I did it!
Wow! Amazing!
Next, we can...
Enough! I can do the rest!
Aww.
Really?
Senpai... Did you...
Isn't it cool? A bunny!
Well, I practiced, after all.
If someone who usually never cooks
spends time practicing cooking for me...
That would be...
Yeah! That would be nice... I think.
You practiced?
No! It's nothing!
It's done.
Thank you so much.
Well, you're the one who made
the rice porridge, though.
Hey, scooch in a little more.
Huh?
Come on.
Hey, wait...
You, too, Kannawa-san.
Oh, I'm good.
Hurry! The porridge will get cold.
Oh... O-Okay...
Now, eat up.
As if you even did anything.
Well, I'm digging in.
How is it?
It's good!
Really?
Oh, Yu.
Don't go crying tears of joy just because
Kannawa-san peeled an apple for you.
That's not going to happen.
My big brother tears up so easily.
Just the other day,
he was crying while playing some game.
Which game?
That game I was talking to you about.
When I played it, I started crying.
I know how you feel.
You can't help it!
What is it?
Sorry!
We must be boring you,
talking about stuff like this.
Not at all! It's just that...
Yu's clearly happier since
you came over, Kannawa-san.
Hey! I told you to cut that out!
What? Why, though?
I know! Want to take a look
at his photo albums?
What? Like she'd want to see those.
I do!
What?
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL GRADUATION "MEMORIES"
MIDDLE SCHOOL COMMEMORATIVE ALBUM
Let's start with this one.
BESTIES
YU IS SUCH A BIG BROTHER
AT THE USUAL PARK
Little Kamegawa is cute, too.
Little Kamegawa... "too"?!
Wasn't my big brother adorable back then?
SEEING THE BLOSSOMS WITH THE FAMILY
A TRIP TO THE POOL
He really doesn't like it.
What? Has he told people
at his work about that?
I heard that he can be quite picky.
Hmm...
Wh-What?
Nothin'.
This is from your birthday party.
You've had a lot of friends
from a young age, Kamegawa.
BIRTHDAY PARTY WITH FRIENDS
Speaking of, his birthday's coming up soon.
You didn't have to tell her that.
Now for his middle school
graduation album!
He used to play soccer?
CONGRATULATIONS
ENTRANCE CEREMONY
This looks like it's from high school.
This is from your college days.
COMING-OF-AGE CEREMONY
There's so much I don't know about him.
Which only makes sense...
Oh, sorry for not noticing.
You finished your drink.
No, I think I've stayed too long—
Oh! I'll go buy something, then!
What?!
Please take this opportunity and stay
as long as you'd like, Kannawa-san!
Wha... Huh?!
Hey, wait a minute!
Be back soon!
Th-That spa day we had was fun.
Y-Yeah.
I know it was sudden, though.
Sorry Hotta pressured you into it.
I had fun.
Kankaiji said she'd like to go again, too.
Really?
But I ended up getting drunk and acting
weird in front of you and Kankaiji-senpai...
The same goes for me.
I don't want to be your junior forever!
I don't want that, either!
I really showed you an unsightly side of me!
Not at all!
I was in the wrong, anyway...
Y-Yeah!
It's because of you that
I've been feeling weird!
Huh?! I-I'm sorry!
When we parted ways
after shopping the other day,
you were walking with Yuki-chan, right?!
Uh, yes!
When I saw that, I had the misunderstandin'
that Yuki-chan was yer girlfriend! And...
Wait! No, that's not...
Why would you feel weird
if I had a girlfriend, Senpai?
Wh-Why?
Why...
Huh? Why would I?
I-I'm sorry!
You must have been worried
for me as my senior.
I know!
Would you like some coffee?
You like caffè latte, right?
Y-Yeah.
Can I help you with anything?
It's not a latte, but...
Wow.
I bought this recently.
I wanted to try brewing my own drinks.
This is my first time using it, though.
Your first time?
Yes.
This is from that time...
I really like the design.
Is that so?
Thank you.
Huh?
The incident with that cup.
I never thanked you for it.
I'm sorry.
Even though I was the one who
broke it, you stepped in for me.
Not at all.
You were helping me find gifts. It was on me!
Okay.
Then we'll have Kannawa be the class president.
DREAM
We're looking forward to it.
AZUSA KANNAWA - 10 VOTES
Hey, guys.
Teacher said to line up and wait...
You're next!
I saw it on TV last night!
Wow! Really?
Nishiura! What the heck are ya doin'?!
Are ya okay?
Yer the worst!
Hey! I told y'all to cut it out!
I'm not really good at
interacting with other people.
But if others were scared of me,
it meant I didn't have to interact with them.
In fact, it was easier for me that way.
But...
Once you became my junior,
I couldn't think like that anymore.
I started brainstormin' about
how to get along with you.
But I couldn't get it right.
I thought, "Oh, I've been running away
from facing my fears this whole time."
That's not true.
You weren't running away.
You were doing your best.
Thanks.
This is kind of embarrassing.
Talking about myself, I mean.
I want to know more about y—
You must be tired from all the talking.
You should rest.
I'm okay.
Go on and sleep.
But...
Sleep...
Are you asleep?
I can't.
Guess it can't be helped.
If you're having that much trouble,
should I sing you a lullaby...
Yu-chan?
Just kidding.
Please do!
Rock-a-bye baby...
On the tree top...
When the wind blows...
Okay, go to sleep already!
What a mess.
A premature gray hair.
YUKI KAMEGAWA: I'M HEADING BACK SOON!
READY FOR ME TO BE BACK?!
Sorry! I came to look after you,
but I ended up falling asleep, too.
Th-This is, um...
Thank you.
Huh?
Oh, um...
You cleaned my room for me, right?
Y-Yeah...
If I knew you were coming over,
I would have cleaned up the place.
What is he...
I was able to sleep soundly
because you held my hand.
I want to know.
Tell me!
Everything about yourself! Tell me!
Foods you like and dislike.
Your favorite manga. Your shoe size.
Which part of a taiyaki do you eat first?
U-Um...
And also... um, uh...
Anyway, I want to know!
About you!
Yes.
I also want to know more
about you, Senpai.
What do you think about us becoming friends?
Friends?
Does that mean I can just ask you to lunch
without asking you a bunch of questions?
Of course.
O-Or for drinks?
Let's go sometime.
When there's nothing going on,
I can send you a photo of a cat
I saw in the neighborhood?
Please do!
I see.
See you.
You, too, Yuki-chan.
Yeah!
I'm excited to go to cooking classes
with you, Kannawa-senpai!
Me, too.
What? When did you two make plans?
Hey.
Want to grab lunch together sometime?
As friends?
Yes!
Great!
She said "as friends."
You got rejected?
Nope!
Instead of a senpai and junior relationship,
we're seeing each other
as friends from now on.
What? What's that all about?!
Bro, you're so lame.